Neufeld, Maurice Papers /3007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I. CORRESPONDENCE/ADMINISTRATIVE FILES
  - Courses - ILR 431, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 42-44)
    Spring 1965. Syllabi, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 431, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Spring 1967. Syllabi, course handouts, and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 431, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 2-6)
    Spring 1967 - Student Reports
  - Courses - ILR 451, 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Courses - ILR 499, 1953-1982 (Box 16, Folder 8-10)
    Student papers and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 506, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Course description and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 506 (554), 1959 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Fall 1959. Syllabi and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 506 (554), 1961 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Fall 1961. Syllabi, exams, and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 506, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    Fall 1962. Syllabi and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 506, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    Fall 1963. Syllabi, course description, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 506, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    Fall 1965. Syllabi and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 506, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Fall 1966. Syllabi, course description and handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 506, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Fall 1968. Syllabi and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 506, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 19-20)
    Fall 1968 - Student Reports
  - Courses - ILR 530, 1960-1963 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Courses - ILR 530, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    Fall 1964. Course handouts, exams, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 530, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 23-24)
    Fall 1965. Syllabi, course handouts, student reports, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 531, 1961-1966 (Box 16, Folder 25-26)
  - Courses - ILR 531, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Courses - ILR 531, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 28-31)
    Spring 1966. Syllabi, course handouts, student reports, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 550, 1950-1954 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Courses - ILR 550, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Courses - ILR 550, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    Fall 1957. Syllabus and exam
  - Courses - ILR 550, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 35-36)
    Fall 1958. Syllabi, course handouts, exams, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 550, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    Fall 1960. Syllabus, exams, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 604 (509), 1968 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    Fall 1968. Syllabi, course handouts and descriptions, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 604 (509), 1968 (Box 16, Folder 39-41)
  - Courses - ILR 604 (509), 1969 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    Spring 1969. Syllabi, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 604 (509), 1969 (Box 16, Folder 43-45)
    Spring 1969 - Student Reports.
  - Courses - ILR 604 (509), 1969 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Fall 1969 - Section A. Syllabi, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 604 (509), 1969 (Box 17, Folder 2-4)
    Fall 1969 - Section A -Student Reports.
  - Courses - ILR 604 (509), 1969 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Fall 1969 - Section B. Syllabi, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 604 (509), 1969 (Box 17, Folder 6-8)
    Fall 1969 - Section B -Student Reports.
  - Courses - ILR 604 (509), 1970 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    Spring 1970. Syllabus, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 604 (509), 1970 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    Fall 1970. Syllabi, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 604 (509), 1971 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Spring 1971. Syllabus, course handouts, and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 604 (509), 1972 (Box 17, Folder 12-13)
    Spring 1972. Syllabi, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 604 (509), 1973 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    Spring 1973. Syllabi, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 604, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    Spring 1975. Syllabi, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 604, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    Spring 1976. Syllabi, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 606 (452, 507, 552), 1952-1972 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    Syllabus, course description and handouts, and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 606 (452, 552), 1958 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    Spring 1958. Syllabi, exams, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 606 (452, 552), 1959 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    Spring 1959. Syllabi, exams, and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 606 (507), 1963 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    Spring 1963. Syllabi, exams, and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 606 (507), 1964 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    Spring 1964. Syllabi, course description, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 606 (507), 1966 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    Spring 1966. Syllabi, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 606 (507), 1967 (Box 17, Folder 23-25)
    Spring 1967. Syllabi, course handouts and description, student reports, and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 606 (507), 1969 (Box 17, Folder 26-27)
    Spring 1969. Syllabi, course handouts, exams, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 606 (507), 1969 (Box 17, Folder 28-32)
  - Courses - ILR 606 (507), 1970 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    Spring 1970. Syllabi, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 606 (507), 1971 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    Spring 1971. Syllabus, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 606 (507), 1972 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    Spring 1972. Syllabus, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 606 (507), 1973 (Box 17, Folder 36-39)
    Spring 1973. Syllabus, course handouts, student papers, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 606, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 40-41)
    Spring 1975. Syllabus, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 650, 1948-1959 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Syllabi, course handouts, and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 650, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Spring 1962 (McKelvey and MFN). Syllabus and course handouts
  - Courses - ILR 652; ILR 653 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Press release and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Courses - ILR 654, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Fall 1956. Syllabus and course handouts.
  - Courses - ILR 654, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Fall 1958. Syllabus
  - Courses - ILR 690, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Fall 1963 (Friedland and MFN). Syllabi, course description and handouts, and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 690, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
    Fall 1964 (Friedland and MFN). Syllabus, course descriptions and handouts, and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 690; ILR 692 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    Syllabi, exam, and routine correspondence.
  - Courses - ILR 702 (505), 1967-1970 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Courses - ILR 702 (505), 1971 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    Fall 1971. Syllabi, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 702 (505), 1972 (Box 18, Folder 12-13)
    Fall 1972. Syllabi, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 702 (704), 1973 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    Fall 1973. Syllabus, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 702, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    Fall 1974. Syllabi, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 702, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    Fall 1975. Syllabi, course handouts, student reports, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - ILR 702, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    Fall 1976. Syllabus, course handouts, and routine correspondence
  - Courses - Independent Studies (Non ILRies), 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 18-22)
    Student papers and routine correspondence
  - Courses - Other Universities and Colleges, 1967-1972 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    Brochures and routine correspondence
  - Courses - Work Training Program, 1946-1955 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    Brochures and routine correspondence.
  - Day, Edmund Ezra, 1946-1951 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    "In Tribute to Edmund Ezra Day" and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings.
  - Dean - ILR - Catherwood, Martin P., 1947-1979 (Box 18, Folder 26-29)
    Memorial statements, memo from Martin P. Catherwood to ILR staff re Martin P. Catherwood's resignation as dean and acceptance of the position of New York State Industrial Commissioner [12/29/58], memo from Martin P. Catherwood to faculty re preparations for modifying the ILR course offerings in the event of war [7/25/50], and routine correspondence.
  - Dean - ILR - Mcconnell, John W., 1959-1962 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    Corres from MFN to Mcconnell (MFN wrote, "I look forward to working closely with you for the years ahead to make our School the undisputed best in the country.") [4/17/61], corres from Mcconnell to MFN re Mcconnell's appointment as dean (Mcconnell wrote, "I feel my primary responsibility will be that of creating an environment in the School where each of us will want to do his best work, and where excellence will have its appropriate rewards.") [6/30/59], and routine correspondence.
  - Dean - ILR - McKersie, Robert B., 1971-1979 (Box 18, Folder 31-32)
    Faculty vote reappointing McKersie to a second five- year term [11/21/75], corres re Faculty Council of Representatives Speaker J.H. Whitlock's ruling that McKersie's published paper on Affirmative Action was a breach of decorum, including memo from Corson to faculty re Corson's criticism of FCR's censure of McKersie [4/14/72], memo from McKersie to faculty and staff re McKersie's appointment as dean [5/20/71], and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings.
  - Dean - ILR - Moore, David G., 1963-1970 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    Memo from Moore to faculty and staff re Moore's decision to resign [9/29/70], and routine correspondence
  - Dean - ILR - Rehmus, Charles M., 1978-1985 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    Memo from Rehmus to faculty and staff re Rehmus' decision to retire [11/9/84], and routine correspondence.
  - Energin, Dogan (former Ph.D. student) - Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    Term reports, research proposal, exam, and routine correspondence.
  - Extension, 1946-1959 (Box 18, Folder 36-39)
    Conference schedules and programs and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Extension, 1960-1966 (Box 18, Folder 40-43)
    Corres from MFN to Risley re Risley's appointment as Assistant Dean for Extension and Public Service (MFN wrote, "Certainly, you are freer now to begin to lead the Extension program of the School in the direction you have long contemplated.") [5/20/65], corres from Moore to faculty re Risley's appointment [5/14/65], conference programs and schedules, and routine correspondence.
  - Extension, 1967-1979 (Box 19, Folder 1-7)
    Conference programs, course descriptions, and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings and articles.
  - Extension - Courses - Credit, 1975-1979 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Syllabi, course handout, and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Extension - Futorians, 1960-1968 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Conference schedules and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings.
  - Faculty - ILR, 1948-1971 (Box 19, Folder 10-11)
    Faculty rosters and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Faculty - ILR - Legislation, 1948-1971 (Box 19, Folder 12-18)
    Faculty legislation, including periodic revisions.
  - Faculty - ILR - Personnel Policy (Appointments and Promotion), 1961-1967 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Guidelines and practices
  - Friedman, Mark (former M.S. student) - Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 19, Folder 20-21)
    Exams and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Grievance Procedure - ILR, 1951-1975 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Cornell bylaws, excerpt from faculty handbook, ILR grievance procedure, and ILR personnel policy guidelines and procedures.
  - Hardman, J.B.S. (labor editor and writer), 1947-1972 (Box 19, Folder 23-24)
    Routine correspondence, including corres re Hardman's term as a visiting professor in Spring, 1955. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Hayes, James (former M.S. student), 1971-1975 (Box 19, Folder 25-26)
    Papers and routine correspondence.
  - Hebrew University (Also Weizman Institute), 1949-1951 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - History, Organization, and Administration - ILR, 1946-1979 (Box 19, Folder 28-32)
    Corres from MFN to Sandra Feldman, Director of Staff, Local 2, UFT, re MFN's finding that NYSSILR "first offered a course in industrial relations for teachers of social studies during the summer session of 1950" [6/17/77], faculty photographs, memo from Moore to ILR faculty and staff re Moore's resignation as dean [9/28/70], memos re ILR student convocations in April, 1969, "The New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations" by James 0. Morris, and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - History, Organization, and Administration - ILR - Oral, 1962-1968 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Humanities, National Endowment for the, 1978-1984 (Box 19, Folder 34-36)
    Application reviews by MFN and routine correspondence
  - Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Institute of International Industrial and Labor Relations, 1955-1968 (Box 20, Folder 1-5)
  - Institute of International Industrial and Labor Relations - Europe, 1964-1972 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Institute of International Industrial and Labor Relations - Far East, 1961-1967 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Institute of International Industrial and Labor Relations - India & Central Asia, 1962-1965 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Institute of International Industrial and Labor Relations - Indonesia, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Institute of International Industrial and Labor Relations - Latin America, 1958-1960 (Box 20, Folder 10-12)
    Memo from MFN re classes taught by MFN to Chilean labor leaders in 1960 [7/25/60] and routine correspondence.
  - Institute of International Industrial and Labor Relations - Latin America, 1961-1965 (Box 20, Folder 13-15)
  - Institute of International Industrial and Labor Relations - Middle East, 1958-1968 (Box 20, Folder 16-17)
  - International Studies Center, 1961-1967 (Box 20, Folder 18-22)
  - International Studies Center - Cornell Aeronautical Lab - CUCIS Proposal, 1961-1973 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    Consultant Agreement between Laboratory and MFN [2/6/62], "A Proposal for Study of United States Employment of Unilateral Arms Control Measures" [2/15/62], and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings.
  - International Studies Center - Foreign Policy Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 20, Folder 24-30)
    Corres from Sen. Fulbright to Prof. Urie Bronfenbrenner re Fulbright's admiration of Bronfenbrenner's speech (Fulbright wrote, "... I am forwarding it today to Mr. Theodore Sorensen, the President's principal adviser on speeches.") [9/22/61], drafts of speeches, papers, reports, and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings and articles.
  - International University of Social Studies, Rome, 1955-1973 (Box 20, Folder 31-33)
  - Isbester, A. Fraser (former Ph.D. student) -Correspondence, 1963-1984 (Box 20, Folder 34-35)
    Photographs, exams, and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Jewish Studies, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    Corres re the movement to establish a Jewish Studies program at Cornell
  - Jones, Dallas L. (former Ph.D. student) - Correspondence, 1952-1973 (Box 20, Folder 37-38)
  - Langlois, Edward (former Ph.D. student) - Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 20, Folder 39-40)
    Papers, thesis proposal, exam, and routine correspondence.
  - Labor Historians' Newsletter (Labor Historians' Bulletin), 1955-1971 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Labor History, 1958-1968 (Box 21, Folder 1-5)
    Corres re MFN's editing, including corres from MFN to Richard B. Morris, History Dept. Chair at Columbia University, re MFN's willingness to serve on the editorial board [10/7/58], minutes of Editorial Board meetings, and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings.
  - Labor History, 1969-1978 (Box 21, Folder 6-9)
    Corres re MFN's editing, minutes of Editorial Board meetings, and routine correspondence.
  - Lee, Han-Il (former M.S. student) - Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Library - ILR, 1945-1957 (Box 21, Folder 11-14)
    Proposals and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Library - ILR, 1958-1968 (Box 21, Folder 15-17)
  - Library - ILR, 1969-1979 (Box 21, Folder 18-22)
  - Library - ILR - IRIS, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 23-25)
  - Library - ILR - LMDC, 1971-1979 (Box 21, Folder 26-30)
    routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Lorwin, Val R. (former Ph.D. student) - Correspondence, 1951-1983 (Box 21, Folder 31-32)
    Exams, papers, and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Michigan State University, 1961-1967 (Box 21, Folder 33-35)
  - Michigan State University - Labor and Industrial Relations Center, 1961-1965 (Box 21, Folder 36-37)
  - Military and Naval Science, 1946-1947 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - ILR Annual Reports, 1947-1980 (Box 21, Folder 39-42)
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - AAA, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    American Sterilizer. Routine correspondence.
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - AAA, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
    IAMAW & Morse Chain. Award, brief, grievance, and routine correspondence.
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - AAA, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 4-8)
    Anaconda Industries & USWA. Awards, briefs, hearing transcript, and routine correspondence.
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Arbitration - Private Referral, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 4-8)
    Ithaca Builders. Routine correspondence. Includes articles
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Endicott Forging, 1980-1982 (Box 22, Folder 10-13)
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - FMCS - Cases Withdrawn, 1980-1982 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - FMCS - Ithaca Gun, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 15-19)
    Award, exhibits, and routine correspondence
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - FMCS - Label Processing Corp., 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 20-24)
    Award, exhibits, and routine correspondence.
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - FMCS - Steel Fabricators, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 25-26)
    Award and routine correspondence.
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - FMCS - Watervliet Arsenal, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 27-29)
    Award, exhibits, briefs, and routine correspondence
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Grant and Fellowship Applications, 1959-1973 (Box 22, Folder 30-33)
    Proposals and routine correspondence.
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - History of Labor in American Politics, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 34-35)
    Outline and routine correspondence.
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Ithaca Board of Education - Blue Ribbon Committee, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Ithaca City Council -Community Development Project, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 37-38)
    Staff papers, "Report on the Government and Administrative Code", and routine correspondence.
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - PERB - General, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 39-41)
    Corres from Robert D. Helsby, PERB Chairman, to MFN re MFN's selection as a member of the PERB mediation and fact-finding panel [4/23/69] and routine correspondence
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - PERB - General, 1969-1986 (Box 23, Folder 1-4)
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - PERB, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
    Southern Cayuga. Routine correspondence.
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - PERB, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Endicott. Routine correspondence
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - PERB, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 8-10)
    Jefferson Community College. Routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - PERB, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 11-12)
    Rochester. Recommendations of the fact-finder, routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - PERB, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    Lansing. Routine correspondence.
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - PERB, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 14-16)
    Johnson City. Routine correspondence.
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - PERB, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 17-19)
    Elmira. Routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - PERB, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    Cheektowaga. Routine correspondence
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - PERB, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - PERB, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    Onondaga County. Routine correspondence.
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - PERC, New Jersey -General, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - PERC, New Jersey -Hackensack, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 24-27)
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - PERC, New Jersey -Hackensack, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 28-32)
    Mediator's report and routine correspondence.
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - PLRB, Pennsylvania, 1970-1977 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Sabbatic (1974), 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Speaking Engagements, 1946-1951 (Box 23, Folder 35-38)
    Speeches and routine correspondence
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Speaking Engagements, 1952-1967 (Box 23, Folder 39-43)
    Speeches, photograph, and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Speaking Engagements, 1968-1978 (Box 23, Folder 44-47)
    Speeches and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Speeches, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 1-4)
    Speeches, including addresses given by MFN as Director of the New York State Bureau of Rationing, and routine correspondence
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Technion, American Society for, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Tompkins County Library - Board of Directors, 1980-1984 (Box 24, Folder 6-10)
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Tompkins County Library - Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1977-1983 (Box 24, Folder 11-13)
    Contracts and routine correspondence.
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Tompkins County Library - Services Study, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 14-16)
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Women, Trade Union, 20th Century Advisory Committee, 1973-1981 (Box 24, Folder 17-19)
    Proposals and routine correspondence. Includes articles
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Xerox, 1960-1970 (Box 24, Folder 20-23)
    Notes of 1966 contract negotiations and routine correspondence. Includes articles
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Xerox, 1971-1974 (Box 24, Folder 24-27)
    Routine correspondence, including corres re 1973 contract negotiations and strike. Includes newspaper clippings
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Xerox, 1975-1981 (Box 24, Folder 28-34)
    Industrial relations seminar (taught by MFN) notes and handouts and routine correspondence. Includes newspaper clippings and articles
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Xerox, 1982-1986 (Box 24, Folder 35-40)
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Xerox - Contracts, 1970-1984 (Box 24, Folder 41-44)
    Labor agreements
  - Neufeld, Maurice F. - Personal - Xerox - Quality of Work Life/ Employee Involvement, 1981-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
  - NILE, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Office Procedure, 1946-1958 (Box 25, Folder 4-5)
  - Public Employment Institute, 1968-1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Publications and School Relations, 1948-1980 (Box 25, Folder 7-9)
  - Research, 1946-1950 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Research proposals and routine correspondence.
  - Research, 1951-1961 (Box 25, Folder 11-14)
  - Research, 1962-1966 (Box 25, Folder 15-18)